Finely for lips is lip gloss, very important.
Get a good color, probably something lighter than the lipstick.
What I like to do is put a little on the base of my palette, which is the back of my hand, and sometimes I like to mix in a few colors.
Depending on what you like, I like natural light colors, and you can blend them in with the same brush that I just used for the lipstick just remove some of the residue of the lipstick before you apply it.
Get a good amount there, mix it in, and what I like to do is put it mainly in the center of my lip.
Both on the bottom and the top.
It also makes your lipstick last longer because it gets that nice moist feeling on your lips without drying out.
Because lipstick does dry your lips out quite a lot.
And, get a good amount, spread it around and to the corners of your lips as much as possible.
You want to make sure that you go with something that's nice, natural, and is not going to or draw too much attention to your lips.
And, there you go.